<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Helen The Human</title>
    <link>https://www.helenthehuman.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Helen The Human</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Helen MIller.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.helenthehuman.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Bunnies</title>
      <link>https://www.helenthehuman.com/modeling-bunnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.helenthehuman.com/modeling-bunnies/</guid>
      <description>This is a little app I built a few years ago, and I figured I&#39;d share it here. It&#39;s at the bottom, after all the words. It is inspired by a predator-prey model, represented by the Lotka-Volterra equations, a very simple set of differential equations which model how a predator species and prey species interact, resulting in a cyclical population pattern (when there are lots of predators, prey species population goes down, until they cannot sustain the predators anymore, at which point predator population goes down and prey goes up, so that they can sustain more predators, whose population increases again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I made it</title>
      <link>https://www.helenthehuman.com/how-i-made-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.helenthehuman.com/how-i-made-it/</guid>
      <description>I made a site and published it. The proof is that you&amp;rsquo;re reading this. I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to do this for a while because I&amp;rsquo;ve heard that having a personal website can be useful, and it turned out to be not too hard. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I did:
  I chose Hugo as a static site generator, because that&amp;rsquo;s what blogdown uses, which I might decide to use some day. If I don&amp;rsquo;t, I might change to jekyll, since it has some nice integrations with github pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing to see here...</title>
      <link>https://www.helenthehuman.com/nothing-to-see-here.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.helenthehuman.com/nothing-to-see-here.../</guid>
      <description>This is a preview of what it will look like when I write some content.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>